{
  "react": {
    "results": [true],
    "activeQuestion": 0,
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "When React was realised?",
        "rightAnswer": 3,
        "id": 1,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "June 28, 2014", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "September 2, 2011", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "May 29, 2013", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "December 11, 2012", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What is ReactJS?",
        "rightAnswer": 1,
        "id": 2,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "JS Library", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "Language of programming", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "Program", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Approach", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a stateless component?",
        "rightAnswer": 4,
        "id": 3,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "Operator", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "JS framework", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "Array", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Function", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "State must be ...?",
        "rightAnswer": 2,
        "id": 4,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "Green", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "Immutable", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "Big", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Alive", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Choose right name of React hook?",
        "rightAnswer": 3,
        "id": 5,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "useProtect", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "useProps", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "useEffect", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "useObject", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What kind of programming patterns React is?",
        "rightAnswer": 3,
        "id": 6,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "MVC", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "ACAB", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "MVVM", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "ACDC", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I use TypeScript in React?",
        "rightAnswer": 4,
        "id": 7,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "What is it?", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "I don't know", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "No", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Yes, sure", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "React component is a ...?",
        "rightAnswer": 1,
        "id": 8,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "Building block of application", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "Operational system", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "Technology", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Array with some instances", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "The copy of real DOM in react is ...?",
        "rightAnswer": 2,
        "id": 9,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "ComponentDOM", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "VirtualDOM", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "ShadowDOM", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "ServerDOM", "id": 4 }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "angular": {
    "results": [true],
    "activeQuestion": 0,
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "When Angular2 was realised?",
        "rightAnswer": 2,
        "id": 1,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "June 8, 2015", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "September 14, 2016", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "May 27, 2017", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "April 3, 2018", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Angular2 is a ...?",
        "rightAnswer": 3,
        "id": 1,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "Book", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "Function", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "JS framework", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Site", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What kind of programming patterns Angular2 is?",
        "rightAnswer": 1,
        "id": 1,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "MVC", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "ACDC", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "ACAB", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "MVVM", "id": 4 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AngularJS is older than Angular2?",
        "rightAnswer": 4,
        "id": 1,
        "answers": [
          { "text": "The same", "id": 1 },
          { "text": "No", "id": 2 },
          { "text": "I don't know", "id": 3 },
          { "text": "Yes", "id": 4 }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}
